<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>FirefliesTwo</name>
    <author>Scurvyez</author>
    <packageId>Scurvyez.FirefliesTwo</packageId>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.5</li>
    </supportedVersions>

    <description>
Discord: steveo.o
steam: Scurvyez

A simple, yet... heart-warming revamp of my original mod which adds fireflies to the Rim (as pure visual effects).
Will I be adding more visual effects such as butterflies, embers, falling leaves in autumn, etc.? No.
This mod is about fireflies only. I might make a separate mod for more general ambient effects in the future though.


&lt;size=24&gt;Supported Biomes&lt;/size&gt;
+ [Core] BorealForest, Temperate Forest, Temperate Swamp, Tropical Rainforest, Tropical Swamp, Arid Shrubland, Desert, and Extreme Desert
+ [More Vanilla Biomes] Alpine Meadow, Cloud Forest, Coastal Dunes, Desert Oasis, Grasslands, and Marsh
+ [Alien Biomes (WIP)] Radiant Plains, Delirious Dunes, and Crystalline Flats
+ [Alpha Biomes] Feralisk Infested Jungle and Idyllic Meadows
+ [Biomes! Oasis] Chromatic Oasis
+ [Medieval Overhaul] Ancient Forest, Dark Forest
+ [Regrowth: Core] Temperate Grassland
+ [Regrowth: Aspen] Aspen Forest
+ [Regrowth: Boiling] Boiling Forest


&lt;size=24&gt;Features&lt;/size&gt;
+ Fireflies spawn if...
    - the weather is clear
    - the outdoor temperature is above some threshold, 5C by default
    - the current season is not winter or permanent winter
    - ambient light from sun is less than 30% (so from around dusk til dawn)
    - additional log message pops if you chose a biome not supported
+ Jobs
    - pawns can periodically chase fireflies for fun, 75% base chance
    - will count towards joy/recreation
+ Thoughts
    - good (short-term) memory for being outside while fireflies are active
    - good (short-term) memory for catching a firefly while chasing them, 25% base chance
    - bad (short-term) memory for accidentally squishing a firefly, chance based on several factors


&lt;size=24&gt;Mod Authors&lt;/size&gt;
+ "FirefliesTwoO.NightlySpawningExtension"
    - add to your custom BiomeDef via a PatchOperationAddModExtension
    - specify a value for the "biomeEmissionRate" field, 1 = base/default value
    - less than 1 means a slightly lower final emission rate; greater than 1, the opposite
    </description>

    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>

    <loadAfter>
        <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
        <li>scurvyez.alienbiomes</li>
        <li>sarg.alphabiomes</li>
        <li>biomesteam.oasis</li>
        <li>dankpyon.medieval.overhaul</li>
        <li>zylle.morevanillabiomes</li>
    </loadAfter>

</ModMetaData>